{
    "subject": "resource/James_Dyrenforth",
    "predicate": "property/hasPhotoCollection",
    "object": "http://wifo5-03.informatik.uni-mannheim.de/flickrwrappr/photos/James_Dyrenforth",
    "human_readable": "James Dyrenforth has a photo collection.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9827041029930115,
            "question": "Does James Dyrenforth display his photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9738209843635559,
            "question": "Is James Dyrenforth a collector?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9702277779579163,
            "question": "What are some of the photos in James Dyrenforth's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9461544156074524,
            "question": "What does James Dyrenforth have a collection of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9275132417678833,
            "question": "Are there any special themes in James Dyrenforth's photo collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9253457188606262,
            "question": "Does James Dyrenforth enjoy collecting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8927447199821472,
            "question": "Why might James Dyrenforth collect photos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8889445662498474,
            "question": "Does James Dyrenforth take his own photographs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8698418736457825,
            "question": "What kind of items are in James Dyrenforth's collection?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8351026773452759,
            "question": "How large is James Dyrenforth's photo collection?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Dyrenforth has a photo collection.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1494_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of items are in James Dyrenforth's collection?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1494_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does James Dyrenforth take his own photographs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1494_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might James Dyrenforth collect photos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1494_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1494_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents contain information about Jacob Dyrenforth, an artist who created sculptures exploring collective consciousness and expression. However, there is no mention of James Dyrenforth having a photo collection."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about James Dyrenforth having a photo collection. The documents discuss his work as an artist, specifically mentioning his exhibition \"Stand-Ins for the All-Time Greatest,\" but there is no mention of him owning or working with a photo collection."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}